M Yardan Aqiella

Frontend Developer

081292770221 myardan.aqiella22@gmail.com Jambi City, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Junior Frontend Developer with experience in using Javascript to build website applications with a vision of creating applications with clean code and prioritizing application performance. I like to learn new and popular things, in my spare time I often practice my algorithm by solving some problems.

EXPERIENCE

06/2022 - 07/2022 Frontend Developer - React JS

Alterra Academy Kampus Merdeka - Casptone Project - Learning management System

05/2022 - 05/2022 Frontend Developer - React JS

Alterra Academy - Mini Project - Resepku

EDUCATION

2023 Informatic Engineering

University Dinamika Bangsa

2022 How to be an Ideal Top Search React JS Front End Engineer

Alterra Academy Kampus Merdeka

CERTIFICATES

12/2021 - Present FreeCodeCamp - Javascript

10/2020 - Present Git Course - Progate

05/2020 - 05/2023 Dicoding - Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web Development

05/2020 - 05/2023 Diconding - Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web

SKILLS

HTML	Advanced	Tailwind CSS	Intermediate
CSS	Advanced	GraphQL	Intermediate
Javascript	Advanced	Git & Github	Intermediate
React JS	Intermediate	Redux	Intermediate
Bootstrap	Intermediate	Figma	Intermediate